In the last lecture, we use the router to render some jsx code.
Son dersimizde baz GSX kodunu oluturmak iin ynlendirici kullanyoruz.
and you also learned about exact and that you can render as many routes here as you want.
Ve ayrca exect hakknda rendin ve istediin kadar Routier ileyebilirsin.
Now in this lecture I want to adjust this, I'll comment it out and by the way, you comment in jsx by using
imdi bu dersin iinde herkesin yorumlad ve J.'ye yorum yapma eklinize gre adalet istiyorum. S. X, Slash yldzyla bir blok
a blog comment with /* and wrapping this in curly braces. And now I'll add another route where the
yorumu kullanarak ve bunu kvrck parantez iine sarmalayp imdi hepsini eik izgi olarak ayrtrmak
path should also be /.
iin baka bir yol ekleyin.
I'm looking for an exact match and now however I don't want to use render, I want to use a different
Kesin bir eleme aryorum ve imdi render' kullanmak istemiyorum ancak geebileceim farkl bir zellik
property I can pass,
kullanmak istiyorum.
I want to use the component property and as the name suggests, this allows us to pass a component which
anlalaca zere bu, bu rota yerine getirilmesi gereken bir bileene izin vermemize izin veriyor.
should be rendered in this route's place.
Component zellii kullanmak istiyorum ve adndan da
Now component is not a string so we don't write posts here, that wouldn't work,
imdi bileen bir dize deil, bu nedenle ie yaramayacak ileti yazmayacaz.
component needs to be a reference to the function or class we want to use.
Bileenin, kullanmak istediiniz ileve veya snfla ilgili bir referans olmas gerekir.
So here simply to what we import from the post component what we previously directly used in jsx.
Dolaysyla, basite J'de daha nce direk olarak X olarak kullandmz post bileeninden aldmz eylere basite
we simply parsed this in curly braces like that
bunu aktardk ve parantezleri byle ardk.
and now if I save this and we have a look at our application and we go back to just slash, we do see
Ve u anda bir kasa ve bavurumuza baktmzda ve sadece eik izgiye geri dndmzde,
all the posts loading up here.
burada tm yazlarn yklendiini greceiz.
So this now shows us how we can load components just like with render but with the component property.
aka bu, muhtemelen kullanacanz kullanm durumunda, iletilerde beklenen en nemli eydir.
Obviously this is the use case you're probably going to use a bit more, render is most important for
Dolaysyla bu imdi, render gibi bileenleri nasl ykleyebildiimizi gsteriyor
short info messages.
ancak bileen mlkyle
You shouldn't really render a whole component's code here even though you could technically do that
Teknik olarak bunu yapabilmenize ramen gerekten btn bir bileen kodunu burada
but that will mess up your code, will make it very hard to maintain but loading components like this
gstermemelisiniz, ancak kodunuzun dalmasna neden olacak, ancak korumak ancak bu yl gibi ok fazla
here that is the default case which will use a lot.
kullanacak varsaylan durumda bileenleri yklemeyi zorlatracaktr.